# MARIAM

DARCHIASHVILI

**Graphic Designer** 

ABOUT:

Avid graphic designer and visual artist, with a degree in Graphic Design from The Royal Academy of Arts, The Hague (KABK). An organised hard-worker and quick-learner; with interests in typography, printed matter and curation, but always open for a new experience. My inspiration lays in music, senses, language, philosophy and dark aesthetics, which I often try to incorporate in my work both theoretically and visually.

Believer in power of black, reason and beauty of Classical Art

# LANGUAGES:

- Georgian (Native)
- English (Fluent)
- Russian (Fluent)
- French (Lower Intermediate) rapidly learning at the moment

# SKILLS:

- Honesty.
- Fluent communicative and organisational skills with the capacity for collaboration and critical reflection.
- Strong creative writing skills.
- Fluent in use of most Adobe software, such as - Illustrator, InDesign, Photoshop, Premiere Pro, Audition and After Effects. Proficient in use of Glyphs.
- Handy with techniques of Riso printing, silkscreening and letterpress.
- Intermediate use of HTML and CSS languages. As well as having basic knowledge of Unity and Blender.

### **CONTACTS:**

# **PORTFOLIO:**

The Netherlands

+31 (0) 6 245 09 969 komnen.info@gmail.com

#### www.komnen.com

-

www.behance.net/Komnen www.the-dots.com [Mariam Darchiashvili] www.linkedin.com/in/komnen

#### **EDUCATION:**

# British Higher School of Art and Design

/Art&Design Pre-Foundation

September 2013 - May 2014, Moscow

# Royal Academy of Art (KABK)

/ Graphic Design (BA)

September 2014 - June 2019, The Hague, The Netherlands

#### **SELECTED EXPERIENCE:**

#### OPEN DAY FOR GRAPHIC DESIGN DEPARTMENT AT KABK

/Project management, Communication and Organisation

November 2019 - January 2020, The Hague, KABK

# OJALESHI - WINE LABEL IDENTITY FOR KOLHIDELI GROUP

/Design

October 2019, Tbilisi

#### KABK GRADUATION FESTIVAL - EXHIBITION

/Design and Research, Exhibition Design

July 2019, The Hague, KABK

# S+ËFAN SCHÄFER DESIGN & RESEARCH STUDIO - INTERNSHIP

/Design and Research

September 2018 - November 2018, Amsterdam

# THE GROVE DESIGN HOTEL - FREELANCE DESIGNER

/Design

April 2018 - August 2018, Tbilisi

# VISUAL IDENTITY FOR KOAN HOSTEL TBILISI

/Design

April 2018 - Novermber 2018, Tbilisi

# AMNESTY INTERNATIONAL - DUTCH 50TH ANNIVERSARY - GROUP EXHIBITION

/Design and Communication

April 2018, Amsterdam, Amsterdam Theatre

# DON'T MIND THE WALLS - A POSTER FOR AN EXHIBITION OF KABK FINE ARTS

/Design and Communication

April 2018, The Hague, KABK

# BITS&PIECES - A WEEKLY NEWSLETTER FOR KABK FINE ARTS

/Design and Communication

September 2017 - May 2018, The Hague, KABK

# KABK FINE ARTS OPEN DAY IDENTITY

/Design

January 2018, The Hague, KABK

# CONSOLIDATING SOUND AND IMAGE

/Lecture/Workshop

October 2017, Moscow, Sfera Education

### VISUAL IDENTITY FOR SFERA EDUCATION

/Design

September 2017 - present, Moscow, Sfera education

# **BALANCE BY STRUGGLE**

/Curation and Exhibition Design

September 2017, The Hague, Gemeentemuseum